{
	"data": [
		{
			"question": "What is the main benefit of using the mobile app within the launch pad?",
			"answers": ["Consolidation of communication channels"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the GMB integration in the Launch Pad?",
			"answers": [
				"To capture phone numbers and recordings generated from a google Listing",
				"To instantly engage with customer inquiries using Google search (on mobile)",
				"To generate and provide exposure to customer reviews"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the Stripe connection in the Launch Pad?",
			"answers": [
				"To integrate a payment processor for use with invoices, payment links, websites, funnels, and products."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "When would you use a number pool? (Multiple Choice - Select ALL that apply)",
			"answers": [
				"To identify the best-performing channels",
				"To track phone numbers across different campaigns"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Where can you access the phone numbers section in the app?",
			"answers": ["In the sub-account settings"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of integrating a phone provider within the agency settings?",
			"answers": [
				"To allow sub-accounts users to easily purchase and utilize all the phone features within the CRM (SMS, Calling, Recording, & Voicemail drops)"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the benefit of using the missed call text back feature?",
			"answers": [
				"It automatically sends a custom or default text message to missed callers."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Where can you access the system's missed call text back feature?",
			"answers": ["Business profile settings"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Is a phone provider necessary to test the missed call text back feature?",
			"answers": [
				"Yes, a phone provider needs to be set up for proper testing."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the biggest advantage of using High Level's web-chat widgets over traditional ones?",
			"answers": ["It allows for two-way conversations through SMS."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why is SMS considered beneficial for web chat engagement?",
			"answers": ["It ensures higher response rates."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can the chat widget be added to specific pages within a funnel or website?",
			"answers": [
				"By individually editing each page's settings and adding the widget's code."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which tab should you navigate to create a workflow for the web chat widget?",
			"answers": ["Automations"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What trigger should you select for the workflow for web chat widget?",
			"answers": ["Customer replied"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What information can be passed on to the user in the notification?",
			"answers": ["Name", "Mobile Number", "Message", "Email"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What 'action' in the workflow allows you to send an information to a user?",
			"answers": ["Internal Notification"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "When using the internal notification, which pages can be specified for the redirect when a user clicks on a the app notification?",
			"answers": ["Contact record", "Conversations view", "Opportunity Page"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you access additional payment gateways like NMI and authorized.net?",
			"answers": [
				"Within the Payments section and Integrations tab located in the sub-account settings"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which integration allows you to enable Google & Apple Pay?",
			"answers": ["Stripe Connect"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does the Google account integration in the settings allow you to do?",
			"answers": [
				"Access Google Analytics, Google My Business data, and calendar sync integration"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the QuickBooks integration?",
			"answers": ["To send review links to paid invoices"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Where can you submit ideas for platform and integration improvements?",
			"answers": ["At ideas.gohighlevel.com"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What are the two types of audit logs mentioned in the video?",
			"answers": ["Agency audit logs and Sub-account audit logs"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Where can you find the audit logs in the system?",
			"answers": ["Within the Sub-Account Settings"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How far back in time can you view the audit logs?",
			"answers": ["Up to 60 days"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Is it possible to restore deleted items using the audit logs?",
			"answers": ["Yes, it depends on the action and its limitations."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Where can you access the template library in the app?",
			"answers": [
				"Blogs",
				"Website Builder",
				"Email Builder",
				"Social Planner"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can the template library be enabled for sub accounts?",
			"answers": ["It can be enabled in the Agency Settings."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What difference is there between an agency user and a sub account user when importing a template?",
			"answers": [
				"The agency user sees a GoHighLevel warning notice while the sub account user sees the agency's name."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you check if a user is a sub account user?",
			"answers": [
				"Check the user's profile in the app within the settings > staff tab"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the difference between a custom value and a custom field?",
			"answers": [
				"Custom values are global fields, while custom fields are contact dependent."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Can custom values be different for each contact or lead?",
			"answers": ["No, custom values are the same for all contacts and leads."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can custom values be utilized in marketing campaigns?",
			"answers": [
				"To dynamically insert standardized information across campaign assets/ collateral."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does the 'Enable Email Signatures' option allow users to do?",
			"answers": [
				"Append an email signature to all outgoing messages",
				"Include the signature before quoted text in replies",
				"Add an image to the email signature"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Where can you enable/disable the visibility of the Dashboard Stats for the user?",
			"answers": ["User permissions"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which role has the permission to create new sub-accounts?",
			"answers": ["Admin"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "When would you typically need to reassign leads from one user to another?",
			"answers": ["When a user departs from the sub-account"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary purpose of creating a workflow to move leads?",
			"answers": [
				"To facilitate bulk lead assignment between users and ensure that no leads fall through the cracks."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What must be done before removing a user from the sub-account?",
			"answers": ["Reassign the leads from that user to another user"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of marking messages as 'unread'? (Via workflows or manually)",
			"answers": ["To highlight important messages"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can contacts be marked as 'starred'?",
			"answers": ["By clicking the star icon in the conversation thread"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What caution is given about deleting conversation threads?",
			"answers": ["Deleted threads cannot be recovered"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What feature allows users to access detailed contact information from the Conversations tab?",
			"answers": ["Clicking on the contact's name or card"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the main purpose of using SMS and email templates in the system?",
			"answers": [
				"To ensure consistent messaging from user across interactions"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of adding custom values to templates?",
			"answers": [
				"To efficiently update message information across the system where the template is utilized."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "When sending SMS messages, what happens if the character count exceeds a certain threshold?",
			"answers": [
				"The message will be sent in multiple segments (separate messages)"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "To bring in human touch points when necessary",
			"answers": [
				"To bring in human touch points when necessary",
				"Time-sensitive tasks",
				"Approval processes"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following is NOT a requirement for manual call and SMS actions to work?",
			"answers": ["Being on a specific subscription plan"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you handle different outcomes from manual call actions?",
			"answers": [
				"Use branching to create separate actions for different outcomes"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which parameter determines how soon an appointment can be scheduled?",
			"answers": ["Minimum scheduling notice"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the benefit of assigning leads to specific agents in a round-robin calendar?",
			"answers": [
				"It avoids duplicate bookings.",
				"It automatically distributes leads based on the calendar settings.",
				"It ensures that leads get the time they want or allows them to select the staff member of their choice."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What are the two types of scheduling/share links that are provided for a calendar? (3 Dot dropdown options)",
			"answers": ["Permanent and Scheduling link"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary purpose of assigning a specific calendar link to a user?",
			"answers": [
				"To ensure that the lead receives a link to the user's calendar to whom they are assigned."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can a sales agent's/ Users calendar link be included in a outbound message?",
			"answers": ["By adding in the message body"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What should be considered when using automation to send user-specific calendar links?",
			"answers": ["Leads must be assigned to the correct sales agent (user)"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What happens if a lead is not properly assigned to a sales agent (user) when using automation with user-specific calendar links?",
			"answers": [
				"The lead will not receive any calendar link. The message body where the link is will be blank."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary purpose of setting up triggers for different calendar types?",
			"answers": [
				"To automate messaging and appointment-related actions, by ensuring that the trigger only fires when it should."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the significance of specifying 'recurring event type' as a trigger filter within a workflow?",
			"answers": [
				"It ensures the trigger is fired only for recurring appointments"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the essential requirement for the 'confirmed' appointment status trigger?",
			"answers": [
				"It ensures the system looks for a specific 'status' in the appointment trigger"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can 'non-confirmed' appointments statuses trigger/fire a workflow?",
			"answers": [
				"By using the 'new' status filter for the 'appointment status trigger.'"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the 'Calendars and Appointments' tab?",
			"answers": [
				"To provide a way to see each users calenders and appointments",
				"To show a daily, weekly or monthly overview of appointments and calendars",
				"To display daily appointments only",
				"To highlight past appointments"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you integrate your calendar into the system?",
			"answers": ["By connecting your Google and or Outlook calendar"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does an appointment marked as 'unconfirmed' mean?",
			"answers": ["It requires manual confirmation by the user"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is one of the prerequisites mentioned for using appointment booking features?",
			"answers": ["Creating a calendar widget and workflows for reminders"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can users book an appointment on behalf of a contact from within a conversation?",
			"answers": [
				"By clicking the 'Book Appointment' button in the conversation preview or within the appointment tab"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can appointment status triggers be utilized in automation workflows?",
			"answers": [
				"To initiate follow-up actions based on appointment status changes"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you change the starting day of the week on your calendar?",
			"answers": ["Through account calendar preferences"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which meeting link option may not show up if it hasn't been integrated with the user's profile?",
			"answers": ["Zoom & Google Meet"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What's the difference between calendar availability and user availability?",
			"answers": [
				"Calendar availability reflects the business's start time and day of the week, while user availability specifies the user's working hours."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How does user availability impact appointment bookings?",
			"answers": [
				"It influences which team member's availability is considered when a lead books."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why is the first row of a CSV file important?",
			"answers": ["It must not be blank"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What are the contact requirements need for the system to link data back to the contact?",
			"answers": ["An email or phone number"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which field type has case-sensitive and spelling-sensitive requirements?",
			"answers": ["Radio button"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why is cleaning a CSV file important before uploading?",
			"answers": [
				"To prevent sending duplicate SMS",
				"To avoid duplicate messaging",
				"To improve contact organization"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the suggested approach to identifying duplicate values?",
			"answers": ["Highlight columns with conditional formatting"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "If not corrected, how are duplicate records typically handled when uploading the file?",
			"answers": ["The first duplicate is kept"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why is the 'Remove Duplicates' function in Excel not recommended?",
			"answers": ["It removes entire contact records"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Who can access the 'Import Contacts' feature?",
			"answers": ["Location admin"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of using the 'None' option for unique identifiers?",
			"answers": ["To generate unique contact IDs for each row"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "In the mapping view (before importing list), how are unmatched fields handled?",
			"answers": ["They can be manually mapped (custom fields) or skipped"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "When might you enable the 'Allow Duplicate Contacts' setting?",
			"answers": ["When importing contacts with shared email/phone numbers"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the benefit of using contact IDs as identifiers during import?",
			"answers": [
				"It helps create records for contacts using the contact ID instead of relying solely on email and phone numbers as the unique identifiers."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is one reason for exporting contacts and custom fields?",
			"answers": ["To perform data analysis in Excel"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following fields are included in the default export?",
			"answers": ["Name, email, phone B", "Create date, last activity", "Tags"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can additional custom fields be included in an export?",
			"answers": ["By selecting them in the 'columns' menu"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you choose specific contacts for export?",
			"answers": [
				"By selecting based on parameters set in your smartlist or manually checking the box next to the contacts name"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary purpose of smart lists?",
			"answers": ["To segment leads/contacts based on specific criteria."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "In filtering, what is the function of 'and' conditions?",
			"answers": [
				"To combine multiple filters and find leads that meet all conditions."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the 'is not' filter option?",
			"answers": ["To exclude leads that meet a specific condition."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can smart lists be shared with other users?",
			"answers": [
				"By granting access to users within the 'Manage smart list' area."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary purpose of the Company Object feature in the CRM?",
			"answers": ["To facilitate communication within organizations"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the significance of the 'Company Object' feature when dealing with ",
			"answers": ["It centralizes all contacts into a single company entity."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of creating custom fields in the CRM?",
			"answers": ["To store specific information about contacts"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of creating and managing tasks within the system?",
			"answers": ["To remind individuals to complete specific actions."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following statements about task assignment is correct?",
			"answers": [
				"Tasks can be assigned to users, regardless of their connection to contacts."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of using internal notifications for task reminders?",
			"answers": ["To remind users about upcoming tasks."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the restore option in the contacts?",
			"answers": ["To recover accidentally deleted contacts in bulk"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is restored when you perform a bulk restore of contacts?",
			"answers": [
				"Conversation, Notes, Opportunities, Tasks, Appointments, Manual Actions."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you initiate the restoration of contacts individually from the 'Audit Logs'?",
			"answers": [
				"By selecting the 'Force Restore' option for the contact in the 'Audit Logs'"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of custom fields in contact records?",
			"answers": ["To create unique questions and data fields per contact"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can custom fields be organized for easier access?",
			"answers": ["By utilizing custom folders to group related fields."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What advantage does organizing custom fields into folders offer?",
			"answers": ["Better categorization and prioritization of information"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What are bulk actions used for within the platform's contact tab?",
			"answers": ["Handling operations on a larger scale"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What types of bulk actions can be performed in the CRM?",
			"answers": ["Adding tags", "Sending emails", "Importing contacts"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "In the context of bulk email campaigns, which factors can affect the data being returned to the CRM from bulk action(s)?",
			"answers": ["The SMTP provider used for sending emails"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can users hide specific pipeline stages from the dashboard view?",
			"answers": [
				"By toggling the visibility settings located within the pipeline builder"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does marking an opportunity as 'Won' typically indicate?",
			"answers": [
				"The opportunity has been successfully 'Won' and moved out of the open stage."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the benefit of attributing a lead's value within the pipeline?",
			"answers": [
				"It visibly displays the dollar denomination of the lead for the opportunity."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of automating opportunities within pipelines?",
			"answers": ["To streamline and standardize opportunity management"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which automation trigger is suitable for moving contacts between stages?",
			"answers": ["Pipeline stage changed"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does the 'Opportunity Status' action allow users to do?",
			"answers": ["Update the status of an opportunity"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary purpose of creating invoices in the system?",
			"answers": ["To keep track of expenses and get paid for services"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which section of the system should you navigate to in order to create invoices?",
			"answers": ["Payments"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you apply a discount to an invoice?",
			"answers": ["Manually add it after adding a product to the invoice"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which statement accurately describes the current capability of adding taxes?",
			"answers": [
				"Taxes must be manually added to invoices as they are not currently supported on checkout forms."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "In the system, how are taxes associated with specific clients or business locations?",
			"answers": [
				"Taxes must be manually pre-built and linked to corresponding clients."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can taxes be integrated with SaaS payment links in the system?",
			"answers": [
				"Taxes are set up using the SaaS configurator for Stripe checkout."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which payment gateways can be integrated to enable the creation of invoices?",
			"answers": ["Both PayPal and Stripe"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of enabling auto-payment for recurring invoices?",
			"answers": [
				"To automatically charge the same card used for the first payment"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following statements are true about recurring invoices?",
			"answers": [
				"Recurring invoices can be created for subscription-based products.",
				"Discounts can be applied to items in recurring invoices.",
				"Recurring invoices can be scheduled to be sent monthly, weekly, or yearly."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following details are listed for each subscription?",
			"answers": ["Status of the subscription"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Who can access the Subscription page?",
			"answers": ["Users on any plan"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What filters are available on the Subscription page? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": ["Subscription status"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What information is displayed on the Orders page?",
			"answers": ["Customer names, source of order, and order status"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Is the Orders page available for all pricing plans?",
			"answers": ["Yes"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What information about the ordered items can users find on the Orders page?",
			"answers": ["Item names and the quantity ordered"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the transactions page?",
			"answers": ["To track customer payments"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What information is displayed for each transaction on the transactions page?",
			"answers": ["Transaction date", "Payment source"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you filter transactions on the transactions page? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": ["By payment mode"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which section under the account or location should you navigate to in order to find products?",
			"answers": ["Payments"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which payment option listed below does NOT support products? (The user would need to manually input the monetary value)",
			"answers": ["Text to pay"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What Payment integrations are offered in the system? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": ["Stripe", "Authorize.net", "Paypal", "NMI"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which type of products can be added to an order form?",
			"answers": ["Products that have been previously created/ imported"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What determines whether a product is a main product or a bump product?",
			"answers": [
				"A specific option is selected when adding the product to the page where it will be sold"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can users verify the products added to the order form?",
			"answers": ["By previewing the page with the order form"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does the text-to-pay links feature allow users to do?",
			"answers": ["Request manual payments through the Conversations tab"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What payment processor is needed to utlize the 'text-to-pay' links feature?",
			"answers": ["Stripe"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What can users customize when creating text-to-pay a payment request?",
			"answers": ["Product name, price, due date, and additional options"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What are the two main types of coupons mentioned in the video? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": ["Fixed coupons", "Percentage coupons"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What can you restrict when creating a coupon? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": ["Number of redemptions", "Specific products"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What information is needed to enable automatic sales receipts? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": [
				"Title",
				"Receipt prefix",
				"Receipt start number",
				"Email template"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which functionality is not available in payment settings?",
			"answers": ["Customizing payment links"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of adding tax information in payment settings?",
			"answers": ["To specify the tax rate and details for invoices"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of A/B split testing in email campaigns?",
			"answers": [
				"To analyze the success of subject lines and content variations"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the minimum number of contacts required for a split test with six variations?",
			"answers": ["60 contacts"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does the 'version history' feature allow users to do?",
			"answers": ["Restore previous template versions"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why is using email providers like Mailgun or LC email recommended?",
			"answers": ["They have direct API integration for better data tracking."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does RSS scheduling allow you to do?",
			"answers": ["Send emails in response to RSS feed updates."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "In the context of email campaigns, what does the 'unique open rate' represent?",
			"answers": [
				"The percentage of contacts who opened the email at least once."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary purpose of a trigger link?",
			"answers": ["To attribute clicks and trigger actions in workflows."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which type of communication channels can trigger links be used in?",
			"answers": ["SMS and email"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can a trigger link be used to initiate a workflow?",
			"answers": [
				"By selecting the trigger link 'Trigger' in the workflow settings."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Where can you find workflows within the system?",
			"answers": ["Automation tab of the sub account or location"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What are workflow triggers?",
			"answers": ["Actions that initiate specific sequence of events"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does the 'allow reentry' setting in workflows do when enabled?",
			"answers": ["Allows contacts to re-enter an active workflow"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following actions can be performed within workflows? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": [
				"Sending automated emails or SMS",
				"Assigning tasks to users"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does the 'marked as read' setting in communication settings do?",
			"answers": [
				"Marks all outgoing automated messages as read in the conversation tab"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why would someone choose to build a workflow instead of using the default auto-missed call text-back feature in sub-accounts? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": ["Throttle options"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the auto-missed call text back feature?",
			"answers": [
				"To prevent missed opportunities",
				"Quicker response to missed calls.",
				"Capture the leads interest before they move onto the next business"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Where would a user disable the default auto-missed call text back feature for newly generated sub-accounts?",
			"answers": [
				"Within the business profile settings located in the sub-account settings"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the 'No Show Nurture' recipe?",
			"answers": ["To promote rescheduling after no-shows"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What trigger would be required for a No-Show workflow to fire/execute when the appointment status is set to 'No Show'?",
			"answers": [
				"'Appointment Status' triggers with an appointment status filter set to 'No-show'."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why is it important to remove leads from the 'No Show Nurture' after booking?",
			"answers": [
				"To avoid overwhelming users with unintentional messages urging them to book, etc."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you grant a user access to a specific feature if they can't see it?",
			"answers": [
				"Adjust the user's permissions and ensure that the sub-account has the specific feature enabled within the agency view."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "On which subscription plan is the split-testing feature available in the Funnel Builder?",
			"answers": ["All subscription plans"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the process to add a product to a page in the Funnel Builder?",
			"answers": ["Create the product under payments, then add it to the page"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which option is NOT available under the settings section of the Funnel Builder?",
			"answers": ["adding a domains DNS records"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why can't a single domain be used for both hosting a website and sending emails?",
			"answers": [
				"Each domain must have a dedicated purpose to avoid conflicts"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What does DNS propagation refer to?",
			"answers": ["The time it takes for DNS records to be added and mapped"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of a 'custom 404 page'?",
			"answers": ["To handle broken links and user input errors in URLs."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the 'layers' feature within the page builder?",
			"answers": [
				"To highlight specific sections and navigate within containers."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which elements can you add to your page to display videos?",
			"answers": ["Hosted videos, HTML5 videos, YouTube videos, and more."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the 'two-step order form' element?",
			"answers": [
				"It requires users to enter their contact details before proceeding to payment."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you customize the appearance of navigation menus in the page builder?",
			"answers": ["By adjusting spacing, colors, typography, and more."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What can you achieve by using the SEO metadata settings?",
			"answers": ["Optimize the page's appearance on search engine results."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is one of the main use cases of forms mentioned in the video?",
			"answers": ["Collecting data from users/leads"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the 'Analyze' tab for forms?",
			"answers": ["To view and categorize form submissions"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which type of field is suitable for alphanumeric input?",
			"answers": ["Single or multi line"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can forms be added to funnels and websites in the builder?",
			"answers": ["Using the native 'form element' in the page builder"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "When embedding forms in third-party platforms, what is the purpose of the 'Copy Embed' option?",
			"answers": ["To obtain the embed code for the form"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Where would you connect a custom form to a calendar?",
			"answers": ["Calendar customization settings"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary focus of the tutorial?",
			"answers": ["Form-triggered workflow and notification"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of a trigger in a workflow?",
			"answers": ["To activate actions in the workflow"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How does the tutorial suggest redirecting 'users' (not leads) upon clicking the notification?",
			"answers": ["By using the 'Internal action' action in the workflow"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How does the presenter recommend structuring a survey for best practices?",
			"answers": ["Keep one question per slide"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can auto-navigation be disabled in a survey?",
			"answers": ["By configuring it in the survey settings"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the main difference between the form builder and the survey builder?",
			"answers": ["The survey builder has slides"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of setting up a workflow for survey submissions?",
			"answers": [
				"To automate notifications and actions based on survey responses"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why is it important to use filters when creating a workflow for survey submissions?",
			"answers": ["Filters help specify when the workflow should be triggered"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What happens if a survey taker submits only part of the survey and leaves some questions unanswered?",
			"answers": ["The survey data may come back with missing information"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of setting up a workflow for survey submissions?",
			"answers": [
				"To facilitate discussion, learning, networking, and knowledge sharing"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the client-facing portal discussed in the video?",
			"answers": ["To provide a link for customers to log-in or sign-up."],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary function of the affiliate manager portal in the community login?",
			"answers": [
				"To facilitate discussions and learning among community members"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Which user roles have the ability to create new channels within a group?",
			"answers": ["Admins"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "In a group, which roles can approve or decline membership requests? (Select all that apply)",
			"answers": ["Admins"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What happens when a group is archived?",
			"answers": ["All members are automatically removed"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of reputation management in the system",
			"answers": [
				"To manage and improve online reviews improve SEO rankings and keep business content new and relevant"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can users customize the review widget's appearance?",
			"answers": [
				"By selecting customizable options within the reputation management tab, located in the sub-account settings."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can you customize the messaging for email and SMS review requests?",
			"answers": [
				"By enabling the respective options and editing the copy and messaging in the reputation settings section"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the prerequisite for accessing notification settings, as demonstrated in the video?",
			"answers": [
				"Being a user within that sub-account, or being 'logged in' as the user within the sub-account"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How does configuring user profile notifications contribute to workflow management?",
			"answers": [
				"It can reduce the number of internal notifications needed for day to day communications."
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why is the LC Trust Center necessary?",
			"answers": ["To crack down on spam/robo calls & scams"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Who is eligible to use the LeadConnector Trust Center?",
			"answers": ["Sub-accounts who use LeadConnector telephony service"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the initial step to access the Trust Center?",
			"answers": ["Verify the business profile"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Why is it important to use a custom domain for email sending?",
			"answers": [
				"Unlike a shared domain, it provides a dedicated sending domain.",
				"It provides better email deliverability (one of many factors)",
				"Custom domains help establish brand identity"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What should you consider when sending emails from a brand-new domain?",
			"answers": ["New domains require time for propagation and domain warmup"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What happens during the propagation period for DNS records?",
			"answers": ["DNS records may take time to update across the internet"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of the reply and forward settings discussed in the video?",
			"answers": ["To manage the forwarding and reply-to email addresses"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can forwarding addresses be added to the email inbox?",
			"answers": ["By entering them in the email settings"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What happens when an email is replied to using the reply address set in the settings?",
			"answers": ["The reply is sent to the specified email address only"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can users access SMS compliance customization settings?",
			"answers": ["In the sub-account's settings"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What are some keywords that can be used in the opt-out message?",
			"answers": ["Stop, stop all, unsubscribe, cancel, end"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the purpose of including sender information in SMS messages?",
			"answers": [
				"To increase message deliverability and comply with regulatory bodies"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary purpose of unsubscribed links in email communication?",
			"answers": [
				"To provide recipients with the option to opt out of receiving emails"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What are the potential consequences of not complying with email regulations?",
			"answers": ["Account suspension"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "How can users customize the messaging for unsubscribed links when using the default LC email feature?",
			"answers": [
				"By editing the messaging in the business settings within the sub-account"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the primary purpose of trigger links in email campaigns?",
			"answers": ["To track user interactions (clicks) with emails"],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the benefit of using goal events for trigger link clicks in workflows?",
			"answers": [
				"It allows for conditional actions based on user interactions (clicks)"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "In the tutorial, what is the reason for creating multiple trigger links for different campaigns?",
			"answers": [
				"To increase email open rates",
				"To segment users based on their email preferences",
				"To prevent users from unsubscribing to from all outbound email"
			],
			"iframe": ""
		},
		{
			"question": "Onboarding SOP",
			"answers": [
				"Our standard operation proceed for handling an onboarding call."
			],
			"iframe": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/e/2PACX-1vRp0dqvh5T_6HCxZSBCVa3oTQ9FEprzXO_cpF1uqLOdaXSuSsy4rMZXSpQK1ZhjfBL-SA56RqNdu7hQ/pub?embedded=true"
		}
	]
}
